我已经上了十次厕所
That was the 1 0th time I've peed here.
你也跟我们说了十次
It's aIso the 1 0th time you've toId us.
抱歉，你们一定听得很烦
Sorry, it must be hard to hear.
三个宝宝在你的膀胱上 蹦蹦跳跳比较好玩
It's easier having babies pIaying ''Bring in Da Funk'' on your bIadder!
我真是受够怀孕了
I am so sick of being pregnant. God!
我睡不着，除非睡床上 但是又会痛，等于睡不着
I can't sIeep, except on my back, which hurt. So I can't sIeep.
我唯一的乐趣来自咖啡 但它是低咖啡因的因为我怀孕
My onIy happiness is from a cup of coffee...
...which is decaf because I'm pregnant!
菲比，你要吃饼干吗？
You want a cookie?
谢谢你
Thank you so much!
你的情绪起伏还好吗？
So, honey, how are those mood swings coming?
我还没有这个困扰
I haven't had any yet.
本集播出：“史上最差伴郎”
The One with the Worst Best Man Ever
淘宝--PSP影视剧院，联系ID:odovo http://shop34710365.taobao.com
Hey, guys.
AII right, here's the ring.
这就是戒指
我愿意，我愿意，千百个愿意
Yes, yes! A thousand times, yes!
单身派对有想法了吗？
Any ideas for the bacheIor party?
托管戒指办派对前 应该先选个伴郎吧？
Before rings and bacheIor parties, you have to decide who your best man wiII be.
真尴尬，尴尬尴尬
Oh, it's awkward.
我已经找钱德了
I aIready asked ChandIer.
什么？你上次结婚他就当过了
He got to do it at your first wedding.
我以为你会了解 我们认识比较久
I figured you'd understand. I've known him Ionger.
拜托啦，我没有兄弟 我永远都没机会了
I don't have any brothers. I'II never be a best man.
你可以当我的伴郎
You can be the best man when I get married.
我没机会了啦
I'II never get to be a best man!
等一下 制片：塔德史帝文斯
Wait, wait.
我让你当两次 你一次也不让我当？
So you'II be my best man twice, and I won't be yours at aII?
你当然可以当我的伴郎
Of course, you can be my best man.
那我呢？你说我可以当
-What about me? You said I couId. -I'm not getting married!
我又没有要结婚
那是科幻小说要挑战的题材
It's a question for science-fiction writers.
你居然不找我 你怎么可以不找我？
I can't beIieve it's not me.
-How couId it not be me? -I'm not even--
我又没要…我又没要… 剧本：麦可寇帝斯等
You know what? That's it.
好，够了
乔伊，从现在起你当我的伴郎
From now on, Joey wiII be my best man.
帅！不过你真的很烂 导演：彼得邦纳兹
Shame about you, though.
别闹 怎么了？
-Stop it. -What?
有个宝宝在踢 那不是好事吗？
One of the babies is kicking.
不是踢我，是踢另一个宝宝
That's a good thing.
It's not kicking me. It's kicking another baby.
别逼我进去
Don't make me come in there!
有碗公可以借我吗？
Do you have a big bowI I can borrow?
子下面有一个
There's one under the cabinet.
干嘛？ 我们明天要开派对，回见
-Why do you need it? -We're having a party tomorrow night.
你们有打算要找我们吗？
-Are you pIanning on inviting us? -No. Later!
没有，回见
崔比亚尼，给我滚回来
Get your ass back here, Tribbiani!
荷尔蒙
Hormones.
菲比的意思是 你们开派对怎么不找我们？
How come you're having a party and we're not invited?
那是罗斯的单身派对 所以呢？
-It's Ross' bacheIor party. -So?
你们是单身汉吗？
Are you bacheIors?
不是 你们是脱衣舞娘吗？
Are you strippers?
不是 那就抱歉了
Then you're not invited.
那你们也别想参加我们的派对
Then you're not invited to our party either.
什么派对？
What party?
菲比的送礼会
Phoebe's baby shower.
送礼会？ 听起来就很不想参加，回见
Baby shower? That so doesn't sound Iike something I want to do.
你们居然要帮我办派对
I can't beIieve I'm going to have a party.
太棒了，派对耶
That's so great. A party!
我也不懂
I don't know why.
在酒方面我的计划是
This is what I got going for the party Iiquor-wise.
买一大堆酒 很好
-Get a Iot of Iiquor. -Great.
至于邀请名单有你、我、钱德
In terms of the invite Iist, I got you, me and ChandIer.
我会请阿甘 因为我们讨论得很大声
I'II invite Gunther because we're taIking pretty Ioud.
我会去
I'II be there.
派对是为你办的 但我想限制博物馆怪脚的人数
I know it's your party...
...but I'd Iike to Iimit the number of museum geeks.
那就别找人类学家 找搞恐龙的就好
Let's not invite any anthropoIogists. Just the dinosaur dudes.
好，还得买一手汽水酒
We'II need a six-pack of Zima.
你们在干嘛？
Hey, what are you doing?
跟我的伴郎筹划我的单身派对
Just pIanning my bacheIor party with my best man.
祝你们办得比上次好
Good Iuck trying to top the Iast one.
不难，因为这次 不会办在必胜客的地下室
It won't be that difficuIt since this one won't be...
...in the basement of a Pizza Hut.
我是罗斯，必胜客配不上我
I'm Ross, I'm Ross. I'm too good for the Hut.
我得去接儿子，看样子没问题
I gotta go pick up Ben. Everything sounds great.
总之不要太疯，大家聚聚打牌
Keep it on the meIIow side. A few guys hanging out.
不要找脱衣舞娘，好吗？ 没问题
-No strippers or anything. -You got it.
待会见
See you Iater.
好好办不能疯的派对吧
Have fun pIanning your meIIow party.
会有脱衣舞娘，他没说不要
There wiII be strippers. He didn't say anything about no strippers.
他刚就说不要
He just said, ''No strippers.''
我当做没听到
I chose not to hear that.
你看我买了什么
Look what I got, Iook what I got!
居然有这种童装
They make these for IittIe peopIe!
给乡下小孩穿的
LittIe ViIIage PeopIe.
你看这件，我最喜欢这件
Look at this one. This is my favorite.
太可爱了 菲比一定会很喜欢打扮他们
That is so sweet.
Phoebe wiII Iove dressing them.
但到时替他们打扮的不是她
Except she won't be the one who gets to dress them.
因为她不能把宝宝留着
She won't get to keep the babies.
天哪 这真是最令人沮丧的送礼会
My God, we are throwing the most depressing baby shower!
除非送她产后可以用的礼物
UnIess we give her aII gifts she can use after her pregnancy.
像普通咖啡，龙舌兰 一整盒烟
Like reguIar coffee. TequiIa!
-A carton of cigarettes! -She doesn't smoke.
她又不抽烟 心意最重要
-It's the thought that counts. -It's a great idea.
好主意 还有她一直想要的皮裤
And those Ieather pants she's aIways wanted!
她一定会很高兴
She'II Iove that!
这是什么玩意？
What the heII is this?
送我2个月后才能用的礼物 我的心情会好吗？
You thought it'd make me feeI better?
To give me something I can't use for two months?
烂透了
This sucks!
这是谁送的？
-Who gave me this? -WeII, I--
我…我…她们说你喜欢
They toId me you Iike them.
好吧，我错了 这是我收过最棒的礼物
AII right, then I'm wrong. It's a great gift. The best present I ever got!
下一个礼物呢？ 我们都没带
What's my next present?
We don't have anything.
好吧，送礼会结束
AII right, fine, then this is over.
真是的…放什么汽球
BaIIoons!
对了，那个脱衣舞娘…
-Listen, about the stripper.... -Yeah?
叫得好
Good caII!
知道下次要找谁办了吧
So I'II be hosting your next bacheIor party?
我希望这是最后一次
Joey, I'm kind of hoping this wiII be my Iast one.
请注意
A IittIe announcement.
我决定我的伴郎 是我最要好的朋友阿甘
I've decided that my best man is my best friend Gunther.
我姓什么？
What's my Iast name?
中央咖啡馆？
CentraI Perk?
谢谢你没娶瑞秋
Thanks for not marrying RacheI.
阿甘，记得拿衣服
Hey, Gunther! Don't forget your shirt.
那是什么？ 派对小赠品，你看
What are those?
LittIe party favors. Check it out.
（98罗斯盖勒单身派对）
（伴郎乔伊崔比亚尼）
请注意，我的伴郎人选还空着
Just want everybody to know the position of my best man is stiII open.
新娘人选也是
So is the position of the bride.
很好
Great.
有一套，你的脖子沾到辣椒
Smooth, man.
You got some chiIi on your neck.
谢谢大家，今晚很愉快
I just want to say thanks, everyone. This was great!
星期一早上见
See you guys Monday morning.
乔伊，谢了 别忘了拿衣服
-Thanks, Joey. -Don't forget your shirt.
博物馆怪胎，派对结束了
Hey, museum geeks! Party's over.
跟小姐说再见，快点
Wave bye-bye to the nice Iady. There you go.
回爸妈的地下室去
Back to your parents' basement. AII right.
出来吧，来
Boys, come on out. Here you go.
好可爱喔，是你养的？
Look at the birdies! Are those yours?
我不知道可以养鸡鸭当宠物
They Iet you keep chickens and ducks as pets?
我把鸭子训练得很好，你看
And I got the duck totaIIy trained too.
盯着墙壁
Stare at the waII.
几乎不动
HardIy move.
白白的
Be white.
你真行
You are good at that.
今晚很愉快，派对办得很棒
I had fun tonight.
-You throw one heII of a party. -Thanks. It was great meeting you.
谢了，很高兴认识你
要是我有朋友要结婚 或是过生日、过星期日…
If any of my friends ever get married or have a birthday or a Tuesday....
那就太好了
Yeah, that'd be great.
那就再见了
So, I guess, good night.
除非你想留下来
UnIess you want to hang around.
是吗？ 对，你可以跟我的鸭子玩
I'II Iet you pIay with my duck.
跳脱衣舞的
Stripper!
舞娘把戒指偷走了
The stripper stoIe the ring!
钱德，起床 舞娘把戒指偷走了
ChandIer, get up! The stripper stoIe the ring!
什么？ 戒指被偷了
-What? -The ring is gone!
先让我清醒一下
Just give me a minute to wake up for this.
你把戒指弄丢了 你是最烂的伴郎
You Iost the ring. You're the worst best man!
不好笑，怎么办？ 我去睡觉，一切正常
This isn't funny. I go to sIeep, everything's cooI.
等我醒来，舞娘不见了 戒指也不见了
I wake up, the stripper's gone, and the ring is gone!
你跟她上床？ 废话
-You sIept with her? -Of course!
你们两个 菲比
-Hi, guys. -Hi, Phoebe.
我想说声抱歉 我昨天在送礼会上似乎凶了点
I wanted to apoIogize if I seemed a tad edgy yesterday at my shower.
荷尔蒙作崇
Just the hormones.
别这样，我们… 荷尔蒙嘛
-No, we-- -Hormones.
谢谢你们，你们真有心
I wanted to say thank you. It was so sweet.
你似乎好多了，太好了
You seem to be doing much better.
你现在怎样？ 很好
-How are things going? -Good.
最近的注意力都在我 你们呢？
Everything's been about me IateIy. So what's happening with you?
我们正在说 我不去参加罗斯的婚礼
We were just taIking about me not going to Ross' wedding.
有那段过往，我可能很难面对
It just might be too hard, given the history and aII that.
这让我想起当年流落街头时
This reminds me of the time when I Iived on the street.
有人说我陪他上床就请我吃饭
This guy offered to buy me food if I sIept with him.
这两件事哪里像？
How is this Iike that?
我想想…的确不像
WeII, Iet's see. It's not reaIIy Iike that.
因为那才算是问题
Because that was an actuaI probIem.
你这只是高中女生无病呻吟 没人在乎
And yours is just a bunch of high-schooI crap...
...that nobody reaIIy gives!
抱歉，我只是…
I'm sorry. I just thought--
泪眼攻势来了
Here come the water works.
我已经没辄了 我打给仲介站，他们不管
I caIIed the company that sent her, and they don't care.
我打119又被吼 这还不算紧急事件吗？
I caIIed 91 1 and they yeIIed at me. This is an emergency!
我真的很想帮忙 但我打算去看“铁达尼号”
I reaIIy wanna heIp you out, but I got pIans to go see Titanic...
所以我要打119问场次
...so I've got to caII 91 1 to find out what time it starts.
我来了
Hey, guys.
谢谢你，派对办得很棒 博物馆那伙人玩得很爽
Thanks again for Iast night. What a great party.
The guys from work had a bIast.
其中有一个没参加过单身派对
One of them had never been to a bacheIor party before.
另一个没参加过派对
Another one had never been to a party before.
那个结婚戒指
So that wedding ring.
可真漂亮 漂亮吧
-Man, that is nice. -Yeah, right?
我也想买一个，要去哪里买？
I might pick one of those babies up for myseIf.
Where might one get one of those?
那个戒指？
When my grandmother first came to this country...
我奶奶刚来到这个国家时
全身上下只有那只戒指 和一小包衣服
...that ring and the cIothes on her back were aII she had with her.
所以那只戒指可说是无可取代
So you might say that the ring is irrepIaceabIe.
当然，它是我家的传家宝
AbsoIuteIy. It's been in my famiIy for generations.
每个戴上它的新娘 都能幸福到老
Every bride who's worn it has Iived a Iong and happy Iife.
所以简直算是一只魔戒
So you might say it's a magic ring.
被脱衣舞娘偷了
Yeah, the stripper stoIe it.
什么？
What?
你刚才说…
-What did you just-- -I think I heard what he said.
我想我听到了，他应该是说…
I beIieve it was, ''The stripper stoIe the ring.''
“被脱衣舞娘偷了”
偷了我的戒指？我的结婚… 脱衣舞娘偷了我的结婚戒指？
My ring? My wedding ring?
The stripper stoIe my wedding ring?
怎么会这样？
How couId this happen?
原因就在于你说了 “乔伊，你来当我的伴郎吧”
It aII started when you said, ''Joey, you be my best man!''
好，我来报警
AII right. I'm going to caII the cops.
我搞砸了你也不用报官捉我
I screwed up. But you don't have to turn me in.
不是捉你，是捉那个舞娘
-Not on you, on the stripper. -I aIready did that.
我试过了 他们说等侦破所有谋杀案再说
They said they'd Iook into it after they soIve aII the murders.
那就找仲介站
-We'II caII the company that sent her. -I did that too.
我也试过了 他们不肯透露她的真名或电话
They wouIdn't give me her reaI name.
他们说我再打去就要报警
They said if I bother them again, they'd caII the poIice.
我说“你去啊” “就说我掉了一只戒指”
I said, ''You taIk to the poIice, you teII them I'm missing a ring.''
难道一点办法也没有？
So, what are you teIIing me?
There's nothing we can do?
怎么会这样？
-How couId this happen? -Look, Ross, I am so sorry.
罗斯，我真的很抱歉
我们可以再叫她一次 用假名把她找去我的办公室
What if we just caIIed her...
...used a fake name and had her come to my office?
好像不赖，但我们得找戒指
That sounds Iike fun, but we got a ring to find!
菲比，你的茶
Here's your tea, Phoebe.
感觉真好
It's so good.
谢谢
Thanks.
那就好 你喜欢就好
-Good. -So gIad you Iike it.
怎样？茶是她泡的
What? She made the tea.
不是，我刚才阵痛了
I think I just had a contraction.
什么？ 天哪
-What? -My God!
几分钟前就有一次 这次绝对错不了
I feIt one a few minutes ago.
That definiteIy was one.
你不能在这里生 男生搬走之后我还没消毒
You can't have the baby here.
I haven't steriIized the apartment since the guys moved out!
没事，别怕，我来烧水撕床单
It's okay. I'II boiI some water and rip up some sheets.
别紧张，可能是假性阵痛
It's probabIy faIse Iabor.
接近预产期会这样，去拿书来
That can happen near the end. Just get the book.
瑞秋，拿书来 书，好
-Get the book! -The book!
圣经？ 我哪知啊
-The BibIe? -I don't know!
好，很好
AII right. This is great.
钱德，你站到桌子后面
You get behind the desk.
但愿她一进来不会认得你 因为…她怎么会认得你
When she comes in, she won't recognize you because--
WeII, why wouId she?
然后你对罗斯和我打暗号
And then you buzz Ross and I.
你是冈萨勒斯先生 我是王先生
You be Mr. GonzaIes, and I'II be Mr. Wong.
民族大F炉
Diverse.
有人叫警卫吗？
Anybody caII for security?
冷静
You be cooI.
好，哪位是阿甘中央咖啡馆？
Which one is Gunther CentraI Perk?
乔伊
Joey.
我的戒指呢？ 我过世的奶奶的结婚戒指呢？
Where's my ring? My dead grandmother's wedding ring.
你还真冷静
Way to be cooI, man.
你在说什么？
What?
床头柜的丝绒盒里有只戒指 你一走它就不见了
There was a ring in a box. After you Ieft, it was gone.
你们觉得我偷了戒指？
You think I stoIe some ring?
一定是你偷的 少废话，从实招来
We know you took it! Just save yourseIf the time and confess.
你们是少年侦探团吗？
Who are you, the Hardy Boys?
我不必偷什么戒指 我1星期赚1600
I don't need to steaI a stupid ring. I make $ 1 ,600 a week.
你们有人赚那么多吗？
Any of you guys make that?
嫁给我
Marry me.
我不懂，戒指整晚都在我房里
I don't get it. It was in my room aII night. She didn't take it.
她没拿，我没拿，你没拿 那是谁拿的？
I didn't take it. You didn't take it. Then who did?
安静，我们在想事情
We're trying to think.
你怎么会知道是假痛？
I don't get how you know it's faIse Iabor.
你有看到宝宝吗？
Do you see any babies?
你感觉如何？ 还好吧
-How do you feeI? -Okay, I guess.
我不知道 大概是知道快要结束了
I don't know.
I know it's going to be over soon so....
那不是很好吗？你说你受够了
But isn't that a good thing?
-You said you were sick of this. -I know.
我知道，只是通常怀孕完之后 就是当妈妈
UsuaIIy, when you're done with the pregnant thing...
...you get to do the mom thing.
我却会穿着皮裤喝龙舌兰
But I'II be sitting around in my Ieather pants, drinking tequiIa.
有些妈妈也会那样
Some moms do that.
那样更悲惨
That's even sadder.
我知道这么做的后果
Look, I know what I got myseIf into.
但他们现在在我肚子里
It's just that now that they're in me...
我仿佛了解他们
...it's Iike I know them and....
把他们送走时我会很难受
It just won't be easy when these babies have to go away.
我知道，但你并不会一无所有
I know, sweetie.
But it's not Iike you won't have anything.
你会有侄子侄女 那样甚至更棒
You'II have nieces and nephews. That's even better.
少来 不，是真的
-Yeah, okay. -No, reaIIy.
你不必担心他们的大学学费
You won't be the one worrying about saving for coIIege.
或在他们不乖时骂他们
Or yeIIing at them when they're bad.
或在他们吵个不停时 喂他们吃立得宁
Or putting them on RitaIin when they just won't caIm down.
他们逃家会来找你 会找你讨论性的问题
You'II be the one they run away to. The one they taIk to about sex.
你可以当酷阿姨菲比
You just get to be cooI Aunt Phoebe.
酷阿姨菲比
CooI Aunt Phoebe.
我是蛮酷的
I am pretty cooI.
还有，他们一定会爱死你
And you know what eIse? Are they going to Iove you!
他们会爱死我
They are going to Iove me.
谢谢你们…再次感谢
Thanks, you guys. Again.
谢什么
Oh, sweetie.
怎么了？ 开玩笑的
Thanks.
What?
Just kidding.
怎么了？ 天哪
Oh, my God!
又骗到了，你们真好骗
Got you again. You're so easy!
要是它有事… 乔伊，兽医说手术很简单
If anything happens to him--
The vet said it's a simpIe procedure.
所以呢？搞不好会出错 要是它没撑过来呢？
Things can go wrong. What if he doesn't make it?
它会的 要是没有呢？
-He wiII, Joe. -But what if he doesn't?
它这么乖巧
He's such a good duck.
我好担心它
I'm so worried about him!
有人掉了戒指吗？
Somebody Iose a ring?
天哪！谢谢你，谢谢
Oh, my God! Thank you! Thank you so much!
鸭子怎么样？
How's the duck?
它很好，正在休息 你们可以去见它
Just fine. You'II see him in a bit.
太好了
Great.
罗斯，谢谢你这么好脾气
-Thanks for being so cooI. -No, that's aII right.
没关系 当然有关系
You made me your best man and I totaIIy Iet you down.
你找我当伴郎，我却让你失望
又不是你的错 当然是
-It's not your fauIt. -Yeah, it is.
你就不会弄丢戒指
You wouIdn't have Iost it.
你知道吗？罗斯，你是对的 他才应该当你的伴郎
Ross, you were right. He shouId be your best man.
不，应该你当 别吵了
-No, you shouId. -Don't argue.
伴郎是我选的
I get to choose my best man.
你们两个我都要
I want both you guys.
真的？
ReaIIy?
你们都应该陪我站在神父面前
Both you guys shouId be up there with me.
你们是我的…
You two are my--
有一个好朋友就…
I'm Iucky to have just one good--
谢了
Thanks, man.
我去那边看看
I got to go check something, okay?
真孩子气 有够爱哭的
-What a baby! -TotaI wuss.
为什么奶奶的戒指是给你？
-How come you're getting Nana's ring? -Mom gave it to me.
是妈给我的
She said something about it being a wedding ring and that you may not need...
她说有个婚戒比较大 你又可能用不上
...one.
我实在不必说这些
I reaIIy didn't need to teII you aII that.
我觉得不公平 我一直很喜欢那个戒指
I don't reaIIy think it's fair. I mean, I've aIways Ioved that ring.
对不起，我原本会让给你 但艾蜜莉对它爱不释手
Oh, Mon, I'm sorry.
I'd Iet you have it, but EmiIy's gotten reaIIy attached to it.
好吧 谢谢
Thanks.
拿去
-Here you go. -Thanks.
你知道那个戒指 在鸭子肚子里摆了2天吗？
EmiIy, did you know that that ring spent two days in a duck's coIon?
[ENGLISH]